<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Novels Reader</string>
    <string name="my_hero_academia">My Hero Academia</string>
    <string name="magic_and_muscles">Magic And Muscles</string>
    <string name="attack_on_titan">Attack On Titan</string>
    <string name="mieruko_chan">Mieruko-Chan</string>
    <string name="my_story">My Story</string>
    <string name="solo_leveling">Solo Leveling</string>
    <string name="one_punch_man">One Punch Man</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="part_1_rank_e_hunter_rank_e_hunter_seong_jin_woo_no_matter_where_he_went_this_title_always_followed_him_around_jin_woo_s_overall_strength_was_almost_the_same_as_a_regular_human_being_with_the_exception_of_being_a_bit_stronger_and_his_wounds_healing_slightly_faster_jin_woo_was_about_the_same_as_regular_people_in_every_other_aspect_it_was_par_for_the_course_then_that_he_d_always_end_up_getting_injured_he_nearly_died_several_times_too_of_course_it_wasn_t_as_if_seong_jin_woo_liked_being_a_hunter_the_work_was_dangerous_others_made_fun_of_him_and_to_confound_the_matters_even_further_the_pay_was_pretty_pathetic_as_well_if_it_weren_t_for_the_medical_aid_paid_out_by_the_hunter_association_to_the_hunters_in_their_payroll_he_d_have_turned_in_his_hunter_licence_and_quit_by_now_and_live_his_life_like_a_regular_person_unfortunately_someone_like_seong_jin_woo_in_his_mid_twenties_and_lacking_in_any_tangible_job_skills_there_was_no_other_way_but_to_remain_as_a_hunter_if_he_wanted_to_pay_for_his_mother_s_hospital_fee_of_millions_of_won_every_month_should_one_say_that_he_had_no_choice_in_the_matter_that_was_why_even_though_he_didn_t_want_to_he_simply_had_to_participate_in_the_raid_supervised_by_the_association_hunters_operating_within_the_same_area_tended_to_know_each_other_pretty_well_in_the_event_of_a_gate_opening_up_all_the_hunters_in_that_district_would_be_asked_to_come_that_s_why_the_hunters_who_had_arrived_early_sipped_on_the_cups_of_coffee_handed_out_by_the_association_s_employee_and_shared_cordial_greetings_with_each_other_quot_oh_hey_mister_kim_over_here_here_quot_quot_oh_mister_park_what_are_you_doing_here_i_thought_you_were_giving_up_on_being_a_hunter_quot_quot_well_that_my_wife_is_pregnant_with_our_second_child_quot_quot_hahahaha_is_that_so_yeah_for_a_hunter_to_earn_big_in_one_go_participating_in_a_raid_is_the_best_isn_t_it_quot_mister_kim_jovially_burst_out_in_laughter_mister_park_followed_suit_with_a_sheepish_chuckle_before_asking_kim_quot_by_the_way_why_do_i_feel_like_that_the_association_is_calling_on_us_less_and_less_nowadays_did_the_number_of_gates_decrease_or_something_quot_quot_eii_of_course_not_that_s_only_because_the_guilds_are_getting_all_worked_up_over_clearing_the_gates_it_s_got_nothing_to_do_with_the_association_i_hear_that_various_guilds_are_jumping_in_with_both_feet_since_there_is_big_profit_involved_in_this_whole_thing_quot_quot_well_in_that_case_since_this_raid_is_being_supervised_by_the_association_it_should_be_safe_no_quot_mister_park_took_a_glance_around_as_if_he_was_getting_nervous_if_a_guild_was_not_involved_today_that_meant_there_wasn_t_enough_profit_to_be_had_and_if_there_wasn_t_enough_profit_to_be_had_then_that_could_only_mean_that_this_particular_gate_s_difficulty_would_be_low_of_course_nothing_in_this_world_was_100_absolute_it_wasn_t_just_mister_park_other_hunters_were_nervously_glancing_around_as_well_quot_hmm_i_wonder_quot_mister_kim_finished_the_rest_of_his_coffee_while_avoiding_answering_his_friend_before_spotting_a_certain_someone_and_raised_his_hand_in_happiness_quot_uh_he_s_here_hey_mister_seong_mister_seong_quot_other_hunters_also_displayed_joy_at_discovering_that_young_man_quot_ah_hello_quot_it_was_none_other_than_seong_jin_woo_jin_woo_performed_a_simple_nod_of_the_head_at_the_joyous_mister_kim_and_walked_by_after_making_sure_jin_woo_was_well_out_of_earshot_mister_kim_began_sniggering_while_confidently_speaking_up_quot_so_jin_woo_showed_up_then_it_s_going_to_okay_today_too_quot_mister_park_s_eyes_widened_up_and_he_hurriedly_asked_kim_quot_what_was_that_is_that_hunter_seong_jin_woo_really_strong_quot_quot_ahh_right_of_course_you_wouldn_t_know_who_he_is_he_s_a_hunter_who_started_working_shortly_after_you_left_you_see_however_every_hunter_here_knows_who_that_kid_is_by_now_quot_quot_he_s_really_that_strong_wait_why_is_he_working_for_the_association_then_why_not_for_a_guild_or_as_a_freelancer_what_a_sad_day_it_was_for_the_coffee_to_run_out_as_soon_as_it_was_his_turn_to_get_one_quot_why_do_you_persist_on_being_a_hunter_mister_seong_jin_woo_quot_quot_i_m_sorry_quot_jin_woo_lowered_his_head_and_apologised_the_young_beautiful_girl_using_healing_magic_in_front_of_jin_woo_yi_ju_hui_showed_how_unhappy_she_was_with_a_pouting_expression_quot_i_m_not_trying_to_get_you_to_apologise_you_know_i_m_only_worried_about_you_if_you_continue_fighting_this_way_sooner_or_later_you_ll_be_faced_with_a_truly_dangerous_situation_quot_jin_woo_glanced_past_yi_ju_hui_s_shoulders_and_took_a_look_at_other_hunters_fighting_over_yonder_when_one_entered_through_the_gate_one_would_arrive_at_a_place_called_dungeon_the_rank_of_this_particular_dungeon_should_be_around_d_a_dozen_plus_hunters_were_taking_care_of_the_monsters_inside_this_dungeon_without_so_much_as_breaking_a_sweat_unfortunately_for_a_rank_e_such_a_feat_was_nearly_impossible_normally_the_job_of_healing_the_injured_hunters_from_the_back_fell_on_the_healers_since_he_always_got_injured_during_raids_jin_woo_was_rather_well_known_among_the_healers_yi_ju_hui_cautiously_asked_him_quot_perchance_is_there_a_reason_why_you_can_t_give_up_being_a_hunter_quot_jin_woo_resolutely_shook_his_head_he_didn_t_want_to_reveal_anything_personal_to_other_people_quot_i_m_only_doing_this_as_a_hobby_if_i_don_t_do_this_i_ll_probably_die_of_boredom_actually_quot_yi_ju_hui_pouted_even_more_quot_if_you_continue_on_with_this_hobby_of_yours_soon_you_d_be_raiding_a_dungeon_in_the_netherworld_you_know_quot_jin_woo_was_taken_off_guard_from_her_remark_and_ended_up_chuckling_out_loudly_thanks_to_that_yi_ju_hui_s_nagging_intensified_quot_ah_ahh_don_t_laugh_don_t_your_injuries_might_get_worse_quot_jin_woo_giggled_before_asking_her_quot_where_did_you_even_learn_to_say_stuff_like_that_quot_quot_what_do_you_mean_where_it_s_from_mister_kim_waaay_over_there_quot_quot_aigoo_that_ahjussi_really_went_and_did_it_didn_t_he_quot_as_they_chatted_and_laughed_his_treatment_was_almost_over_it_was_already_too_late_by_then_though_it_seemed_that_the_raid_was_pretty_much_over_now_jin_woo_s_expression_hardened_i_only_killed_a_single_monster_today_a_rank_e_creature_no_less_seong_jin_woo_began_fidgeting_with_the_rank_e_magic_crystal_in_his_hand_the_lowest_grade_magic_crystal_from_a_rank_e_monster_fetched_less_than_hundred_thousand_won_for_something_he_bet_his_life_to_earn_it_was_a_pathetically_small_amount_tl_just_over_88_a_magic_crystal_from_a_rank_c_monster_can_sell_for_over_ten_million_won_though_tl_8830_too_bad_a_rank_e_hunter_such_as_himself_couldn_t_even_attempt_to_kill_a_monster_with_a_rank_as_high_as_c_out_of_the_blue_someone_shouted_out_quot_uh_hey_there_s_another_entrance_over_here_quot_the_nearby_hunters_rushed_over_there_quot_huh_it_s_true_quot_quot_there_really_is_another_path_quot_just_as_that_hunter_said_there_was_an_entrance_hidden_within_the_dungeon_itself_quot_a_dual_dungeon_is_it_so_such_a_thing_actually_exists_for_real_quot_mister_song_possessing_over_ten_years_experience_as_a_hunter_looked_into_the_hidden_entrance_and_displayed_how_surprised_he_was_the_interior_of_the_hidden_cave_like_passage_was_dark_and_nothing_could_be_seen_mister_song_activated_his_speciality_flame_magic_and_tossed_it_further_forward_into_the_passage_the_flame_flew_forward_and_illuminated_the_interior_the_passageway_seemed_to_go_on_forever_soon_enough_the_flame_lost_its_forward_momentum_fell_to_the_ground_and_smouldered_for_a_bit_before_flickering_out_of_existence_the_passage_was_shrouded_in_darkness_once_more_quot_hmm_everyone_gather_around_let_s_have_a_meeting_quot_the_unspoken_leader_of_this_raid_mister_song_called_for_other_hunters_to_gather_around_jin_woo_s_treatment_was_over_by_then_so_he_and_yi_ju_hui_also_joined_in_song_spoke_up_while_sweeping_his_gaze_over_the_gathered_hunters_quot_as_you_know_very_well_a_gate_will_not_close_unless_the_dungeon_s_boss_is_killed_since_the_gate_itself_is_still_intact_even_though_we_took_care_of_all_the_monsters_here_that_can_only_mean_that_the_boss_is_beyond_that_passageway_quot_song_pointed_towards_the_hidden_entrance_hunters_exchanged_meaningful_glances_and_nodded_their_heads_no_one_could_disagree_with_that_notion_song_continued_on_quot_now_normally_we_re_supposed_to_relay_this_information_back_to_the_association_and_wait_for_their_decision_first_but_but_if_we_do_that_we_might_end_up_handing_over_the_task_of_killing_the_boss_to_other_hunters_and_our_takings_for_today_s_raid_would_decrease_by_a_lot_quot_the_expressions_of_the_hunters_crumpled_park_s_face_hardened_more_than_anyone_else_since_he_needed_a_lot_of_cash_for_his_wife_s_pregnancy_postnatal_care_eats_up_so_much_cash_nowadays_you_know_at_this_rate_there_d_be_no_meaning_behind_him_risking_his_life_to_participate_in_this_raid_quot_that_s_why_i_d_prefer_if_we_took_care_of_the_boss_before_leaving_this_dungeon_so_what_do_you_all_think_quot_hunters_fell_into_a_deep_contemplation_quot_quot_quot_quot_the_truth_was_no_one_here_could_figure_out_the_current_situation_and_so_their_safety_could_not_be_guaranteed_however_the_difficulty_of_this_particular_dungeon_proved_to_be_very_low_so_the_hidden_dungeon_within_it_couldn_t_have_been_that_difficult_either_quot_hmm_hmm_quot_song_coughed_to_draw_everyone_s_attention_to_himself_quot_since_we_have_seventeen_people_here_let_s_put_this_to_a_vote_shall_we_once_the_decision_has_been_made_no_one_complains_so_how_about_it_quot_others_nodded_their_heads_after_hearing_song_s_suggestion_no_one_was_disagreeing_with_him_quot_i_vote_for_going_ahead_quot_song_raised_his_hand_and_then_other_hunters_began_raising_their_hands_one_by_one_quot_me_too_quot_quot_count_me_in_as_well_quot_park_was_the_first_to_raise_his_hand_followed_shortly_after_by_kim_and_a_few_other_hunters_of_course_those_disagreeing_were_plentiful_too_quot_let_s_go_back_quot_quot_i_feel_that_it_d_be_better_to_wait_for_the_association_s_decision_quot_the_two_opposing_camps_were_neck_and_neck_and_eventually_the_final_votes_came_down_to_jin_woo_and_yi_ju_hui_quot_i_m_sorry_quot_yi_ju_hui_bowed_to_song_and_added_her_vote_to_retreat_camp_and_so_the_vote_count_for_go_ahead_and_retreat_was_at_8_8_a_deadlock_song_asked_the_hesitant_seong_jin_woo_next_quot_and_you_mister_seong_quot">Part 1: Rank E Hunter Rank E Hunter, Seong Jin-Woo. No matter where he went, this title always followed him around. Jin-Woo’s overall strength was almost the same as a regular human being. With the exception of being a bit stronger and his wounds healing slightly faster, Jin-Woo was about the same as regular people in every other aspect. It was par for the course then, that he’d always end up getting injured. He nearly died several times, too. Of course, it wasn’t as if Seong Jin-Woo liked being a Hunter. The work was dangerous, others made fun of him, and to confound the matters even further, the pay was pretty pathetic, as well. If it weren’t for the medical aid paid out by the Hunter Association to the Hunters in their “payroll”, he’d have turned in his hunter licence and quit by now, and live his life like a regular person. Unfortunately, someone like Seong Jin-Woo, in his mid-twenties and lacking in any tangible job skills, there was no other way but to remain as a Hunter if he wanted to pay for his mother’s hospital fee of millions of won every month. Should one say that he had no choice in the matter? That was why, even though he didn\'t want to, he simply had to participate in the raid supervised by the Association. Hunters operating within the same area tended to know each other pretty well. In the event of a Gate opening up, all the Hunters in that district would be asked to come, that\'s why. The Hunters who had arrived early sipped on the cups of coffee handed out by the Association\'s employee and shared cordial greetings with each other. \"Oh, hey. Mister Kim, Over here. Here.\" \"Oh? Mister Park, what are you doing here? I thought you were giving up on being a Hunter?\" \"Well, that... My wife is pregnant with our second child.\" \"Hahahaha, is that so. Yeah, for a Hunter to earn big in one go, participating in a raid is the best, isn\'t it.\" Mister Kim jovially burst out in laughter. Mister Park followed suit with a sheepish chuckle, before asking Kim. \"By the way, why do I feel like that the Association is calling on us less and less nowadays? Did the number of Gates decrease or something?\" \"Eii, of course not. That\'s only because the Guilds are getting all worked up over clearing the Gates; it\'s got nothing to do with the Association. I hear that various Guilds are jumping in with both feet since there is big profit involved in this whole thing.\" \"Well, in that case, since this raid is being supervised by the Association, it should be safe, no?\" Mister Park took a glance around as if he was getting nervous. If a Guild was not involved today, that meant there wasn\'t enough profit to be had, and if there wasn\'t enough profit to be had, then that could only mean that this particular Gate\'s difficulty would be low. Of course, nothing in this world was 100% absolute. It wasn\'t just Mister Park; other Hunters were nervously glancing around as well. \"Hmm. I wonder....\" Mister Kim finished the rest of his coffee while avoiding answering his friend, before spotting a certain someone and raised his hand in happiness. \"Uh! He\'s here. Hey, Mister Seong!! Mister Seong!!\" Other Hunters also displayed joy at discovering that young man. \"Ah, hello.\" It was none other than Seong Jin-Woo. Jin-Woo performed a simple nod of the head at the joyous Mister Kim and walked by. After making sure Jin-Woo was well out of earshot, Mister Kim began sniggering while confidently speaking up. \"So, Jin-Woo showed up. Then it\'s going to okay today, too.\" Mister Park\'s eyes widened up and he hurriedly asked Kim. \"What was that? Is that Hunter Seong Jin-Woo really strong?\" \"Ahh. Right, of course, you wouldn\'t know who he is. He\'s a Hunter who started working shortly after you left, you see. However, every Hunter here knows who that kid is by now.\" \"He\'s really that strong? Wait, why is he working for the Association, then? Why not for a Guild or as a freelancer?What a sad day it was, for the coffee to run out as soon as it was his turn to get one. *** \"Why do you persist on being a Hunter, Mister Seong Jin-Woo?\" \"I\'m sorry.\" Jin-Woo lowered his head and apologised. The young, beautiful girl using healing magic in front of Jin-Woo, Yi Ju-Hui showed how unhappy she was with a pouting expression. \"I\'m not trying to get you to apologise, you know? I\'m only worried about you. If you continue fighting this way, sooner or later you\'ll be faced with a truly dangerous situation.\" Jin-Woo glanced past Yi Ju-Hui\'s shoulders and took a look at other Hunters fighting over yonder. When one entered through the Gate, one would arrive at a place called \'dungeon\'. The rank of this particular dungeon should be around D. A dozen-plus Hunters were taking care of the monsters inside this dungeon without so much as breaking a sweat. Unfortunately, for a rank E, such a feat was nearly impossible. Normally, the job of healing the injured Hunters from the back fell on the Healers. Since he always got injured during raids, Jin-Woo was rather well-known among the Healers. Yi Ju-Hui cautiously asked him. \"Perchance, is there a reason why you can\'t give up being a Hunter?\" Jin-Woo resolutely shook his head. He didn\'t want to reveal anything personal to other people. \"I\'m only doing this as a hobby. If I don\'t do this, I\'ll probably die of boredom, actually.\" Yi Ju-Hui pouted even more. \"If you continue on with this hobby of yours, soon you\'d be raiding a dungeon in the netherworld, you know?\"Jin-Woo was taken off-guard from her remark and ended up chuckling out loudly. Thanks to that, Yi Ju-Hui\'s nagging intensified. \"Ah, ahh!! Don\'t laugh! Don\'t! Your injuries might get worse!!\" Jin-Woo giggled before asking her. \"Where did you even learn to say stuff like that?\" \"What do you mean, where? It\'s from Mister Kim waaay over there.\" \"Aigoo, that ahjussi really went and did it, didn\'t he....\" As they chatted and laughed, his treatment was almost over. It was already too late by then, though. It seemed that the raid was pretty much over now. Jin-Woo\'s expression hardened. \'I only killed a single monster today.\' A rank E creature, no less. Seong Jin-Woo began fidgeting with the rank E magic crystal in his hand. The lowest grade magic crystal from a rank E monster fetched less than hundred thousand won. For something he bet his life to earn, it was a pathetically small amount. (TL: Just over $88.) \'A magic crystal from a rank C monster can sell for over ten million won, though....\' (TL: $8830+) Too bad, a rank E Hunter such as himself couldn\'t even attempt to kill a monster with a rank as high as C. Out of the blue, someone shouted out. \"Uh? Hey, there\'s another entrance over here.\" The nearby Hunters rushed over there. \"Huh, it\'s true.\" \"There really is another path?\" Just as that Hunter said, there was an entrance hidden within the dungeon itself. \"A dual dungeon, is it... So, such a thing actually exists for real....\" Mister Song, possessing over ten years\' experience as a Hunter, looked into the hidden entrance and displayed how surprised he was. The interior of the hidden, cave-like passage was dark and nothing could be seen. Mister Song activated his speciality, flame magic, and tossed it further forward into the passage.The flame flew forward and illuminated the interior. The passageway seemed to go on forever. Soon enough, the flame lost its forward momentum, fell to the ground and smouldered for a bit before flickering out of existence. The passage was shrouded in darkness once more. \"Hmm..... Everyone, gather around. Let\'s have a meeting.\" The unspoken leader of this raid, Mister Song, called for other Hunters to gather around. Jin-Woo\'s treatment was over by then, so he and Yi Ju-Hui also joined in. Song spoke up while sweeping his gaze over the gathered Hunters. \"As you know very well, a Gate will not close unless the dungeon\'s boss is killed. Since the Gate itself is still intact even though we took care of all the monsters here, that can only mean that the boss is beyond that passageway.\" Song pointed towards the hidden entrance. Hunters exchanged meaningful glances and nodded their heads. No one could disagree with that notion. Song continued on. \"Now normally, we\'re supposed to relay this information back to the Association and wait for their decision first, but... But, if we do that, we might end up handing over the task of killing the boss to other Hunters, and our takings for today\'s raid would decrease by a lot.\" The expressions of the Hunters crumpled. Park\'s face hardened more than anyone else since he needed a lot of cash for his wife\'s pregnancy. \'Postnatal care eats up so much cash nowadays, you know...\' At this rate, there\'d be no meaning behind him risking his life to participate in this raid. \"That\'s why I\'d prefer if we took care of the boss before leaving this dungeon... So, what do you all think?\" Hunters fell into a deep contemplation. \"....\" \"....\" The truth was, no one here could figure out the current situation and so, their safety could not be guaranteed. However, the difficulty of this particular dungeon proved to be very low. So, the hidden dungeon within it couldn\'t have been that difficult, either. \"Hmm, hmm.\" Song coughed to draw everyone\'s attention to himself. \"Since we have seventeen people here, let\'s put this to a vote, shall we? Once the decision has been made, no one complains. So? How about it?\" Others nodded their heads after hearing Song\'s suggestion. No one was disagreeing with him. \"I vote for going ahead.\" Song raised his hand. And then, other Hunters began raising their hands one by one. \"Me too.\" \"Count me in as well.\" Park was the first to raise his hand, followed shortly after by Kim and a few other Hunters. Of course, those disagreeing were plentiful, too. \"Let\'s go back.\" \"I feel that it\'d be better to wait for the Association\'s decision.\" The two opposing camps were neck and neck and eventually, the final votes came down to Jin-Woo and Yi Ju-Hui. \"I\'m sorry....\" Yi Ju-Hui bowed to Song and added her vote to \'retreat\' camp. And so, the vote count for \'go ahead\' and \'retreat\' was at 8:8. A deadlock. Song asked the hesitant Seong Jin-Woo next. \"And you, Mister Seong?\"</string>
    <string name="read">Read</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="sololeveling">Solo Leveling</string>
    <string name="to_do">TODO</string>
    <string name="jujutsu_kaisen">Jujutsu_Kaisen</string>
    <string name="chapter_1_the_only_friend_quot_suguru_wait_for_me_quot_a_breathless_voice_shouted_out_loud_racing_to_catch_up_with_suguru_a_tiny_figure_approached_him_quot_sana_what_are_you_doing_here_quot_suguru_didn_t_expected_her_to_be_here_quot_see_isn_t_it_such_a_good_surprise_that_i_m_here_now_we_both_can_be_together_during_holidays_as_well_hehehe_quot_she_grinned_as_she_said_this_suguru_cast_a_suspicious_glance_at_his_mother_she_averted_her_eyes_while_smiling_it_was_obvious_that_the_one_who_told_sana_about_their_holiday_destination_was_suguru_s_mom_quot_suguru_isn_t_it_nice_your_friend_is_also_here_now_you_both_won_t_miss_each_other_during_holidays_quot_she_said_with_a_loving_smile_on_her_face_quot_i_wasn_t_going_to_miss_her_anyway_quot_he_said_with_a_frowning_face_quot_neither_was_i_it_is_the_worst_coincidence_ever_quot_she_went_away_with_a_saddened_face_quot_suguru_you_should_apologize_to_her_she_was_so_happy_to_see_you_quot_suguru_s_mother_gave_him_a_mild_scolding_suguru_went_after_sana_to_apologize_quot_i_m_sorry_sana_i_didn_t_mean_to_hurt_you_let_us_play_together_quot_suguru_said_as_soon_as_he_caught_her_pace_quot_no_you_liar_you_totally_meant_to_hurt_me_i_don_t_want_to_play_with_you_you_are_here_just_because_you_don_t_want_to_get_scolded_by_your_mom_quot_she_answered_in_anger_and_started_going_to_where_her_parents_were_quot_wait_you_run_so_fast_it_s_difficult_for_me_to_catch_you_quot_suguru_intoned_as_he_was_gasping_for_breath_quot_mama_papa_let_s_go_back_i_don_t_want_to_stay_here_quot_she_cried_quot_did_you_had_a_fight_with_suguru_again_quot_someone_with_a_sweet_soothing_voice_asked_sana_quot_no_mama_i_don_t_know_where_he_is_i_just_want_to_go_back_home_quot_she_cried_in_her_loudest_voice_quot_stop_shouting_like_that_and_come_play_with_me_quot_suguru_reached_there_and_held_her_hand_quot_hey_you_there_you_good_for_nothing_brat_how_dare_you_made_my_daughter_cry_you_sure_don_t_love_your_life_quot_a_scary_tall_figure_came_out_from_the_shadow_of_a_beach_cabin_suguru_was_too_scared_to_say_anything_why_he_has_to_be_here_of_all_the_people_he_thought_to_himself_quot_dear_they_are_just_playing_if_you_keep_on_scaring_away_everyone_like_that_then_she_s_not_gonna_make_any_friends_and_suguru_is_her_only_friend_if_you_gonna_keep_up_that_attitude_nobody_s_ever_gonna_come_near_your_daughter_quot_sana_s_mother_said_quot_friend_or_whatever_nobody_is_allowed_to_hurt_my_daughter_quot_he_added_quot_papa_don_t_shout_at_suguru_quot_sana_tattled_at_her_dad_quot_what_kind_of_black_magic_has_this_suguru_done_on_my_child_sana_i_m_your_cute_dad_you_can_t_shout_on_me_for_a_stranger_papa_loves_you_soo_muchh_quot_her_dad_babbled_quot_sorry_nakamura_san_quot_suguru_took_sana_s_hand_and_eloped_from_there_as_fast_as_he_could_quot_he_always_takes_away_my_cute_daughter_this_bastard_quot_he_said_while_sulking_quot_now_who_s_behaving_like_a_spoiled_brat_you_can_t_be_the_only_one_who_gets_to_play_with_her_always_quot_sana_s_mom_added_suguru_and_sana_play_till_the_sunset_on_the_shore_nakamura_sana_and_geto_suguru_are_childhood_friends_they_attend_the_same_school_and_also_live_in_vicinity_they_are_not_exactly_neighbors_but_their_houses_are_near_enough_that_they_can_go_to_each_other_s_home_to_play_they_re_both_seven_suguru_is_a_slim_boy_with_black_hair_slightly_long_till_shoulders_with_bangs_and_purple_eyes_cares_deeply_for_everyone_have_a_mom_and_a_dad_nakamura_sana_is_a_bit_skinny_girl_with_dark_brown_hair_and_eyes_she_s_as_tall_as_suguru_cries_when_suguru_acts_mean_towards_her_has_one_friend_i_e_suguru_everyone_runs_away_because_of_her_dad_and_also_she_s_too_shy_to_make_friends_suguru_was_the_one_who_asked_her_to_play_together_when_she_was_playing_alone_in_the_park_while_all_other_children_were_playing_together_they_said_she_looked_ugly_skeleton_and_refused_to_play_with_her_suguru_even_beat_up_one_or_two_kid_who_were_badmouthing_her_and_later_got_scolded_by_his_parents_for_getting_involved_in_a_fight_the_kids_he_beat_up_complained_at_his_home_from_that_day_on_wards_sana_and_suguru_became_very_good_friends_little_kids_are_bitches_agree_jk_suguru_s_mom_and_dad_are_really_sweet_and_they_are_also_nice_towards_sana_they_are_highly_disciplined_people_but_not_too_stiff_to_the_rules_suguru_is_their_only_son_the_three_of_them_make_a_really_sweet_family_sana_have_a_mom_and_dad_as_well_her_dad_is_a_tall_man_with_a_well_built_physique_and_have_dark_brown_hair_that_reaches_his_shoulders_with_an_undercut_he_usually_tie_them_up_he_s_a_sporty_person_has_a_partnership_in_a_yacht_business_oversees_that_s_basically_their_source_of_income_sana_s_mom_is_a_baker_their_home_is_designed_with_the_bakery_on_the_ground_floor_and_the_residence_on_the_upper_story_she_has_a_bit_delicate_body_her_black_hair_goes_down_her_shoulder_and_are_often_tied_in_a_loose_ponytail_she_s_not_that_tall_between_5_6_quot_to_5_7_quot_she_is_a_sweet_person_but_scolds_her_husband_at_times_they_make_a_sweet_couple_he_met_her_at_her_bakery_first_time"><![CDATA[Chapter 1 THE ONLY FRIEND  \"Suguru, wait for me!\" A breathless voice shouted out loud, racing to catch up with Suguru. A tiny figure approached him.  \"Sana? What are you doing here?\" Suguru didn\'t expected her to be here. \"See isn\'t it such a good surprise that I\'m here, now we both can be together during holidays as well. Hehehe\" she grinned as she said this. Suguru cast a suspicious glance at his mother. She averted her eyes while smiling. It was obvious that the one who told Sana about their holiday destination was Suguru\'s mom.  \"Suguru, isn\'t it nice your friend is also here now. You both won\'t miss each other during holidays.\" She said with a loving smile on her face. \"I wasn\'t going to miss her anyway,\" he said with a frowning face.  \" Neither was I. It is the worst coincidence ever,\" she went away with a saddened face.  \"Suguru, you should apologize to her; she was so happy to see you.\" Suguru\'s mother gave him a mild scolding. Suguru went after Sana to apologize.   \"I\'m sorry, Sana. I didn\'t mean to hurt you. Let us play together.\" Suguru said as soon as he caught her pace. \"No you liar, you totally meant to hurt me. I don\'t want to play with you. You are here just because you don\'t want to get scolded by your mom.\" she answered in anger and started going to where her parents were.  \"wait! you run so fast it\'s difficult for me to catch you,\" Suguru intoned as he was gasping for breath.  \"Mama Papa let\'s go back, i don\'t want to stay here.\" she cried. \"Did you had a fight with Suguru again?\" someone with a sweet soothing voice asked Sana. \"No mama I don\'t know where he is. I just want to go back home.\" she cried in her loudest voice. \"Stop shouting like that, and come play with me,\" Suguru reached there and held her hand.  \"Hey you there! you good for nothing brat, how dare you made my daughter cry? You sure don\'t love your life.\" A scary tall figure came out from the shadow of a beach cabin. Suguru was too scared to say anything. \'why he has to be here of all the people\' he thought to himself. \" Dear, they are just playing, if you keep on scaring away everyone like that then she\'s not gonna make any friends. And Suguru is her only friend. If you gonna keep up that attitude nobody\'s ever gonna come near your daughter.\" Sana\'s mother said. \"Friend or whatever, nobody is allowed to hurt my daughter;\" he added. \" Papa don\'t shout at Suguru.\" Sana tattled at her dad.\" What kind of black magic has this Suguru done on my child. Sana I\'m your cute dad. You can\'t shout on me for a stranger. Papa loves you soo muchh,\" her dad babbled.  \"Sorry Nakamura San,\" Suguru took Sana\'s hand and eloped from there as fast as he could.  \"He always takes away my cute daughter, this bastard\" he said while sulking.  \"Now who\'s behaving like a spoiled brat. You can\'t be the only one who gets to play with her always,\" Sana\'s mom added.  **** Suguru and Sana play till the sunset on the shore ******** ***** Nakamura Sana and Geto Suguru are childhood friends. they attend the same school and also live in vicinity. They are not exactly neighbors but their houses are near enough that they can go to each other\'s home to play. *** They\'re both seven. * * **  Suguru is a slim boy with black hair (slightly long till shoulders with bangs) and purple eyes. Cares deeply for everyone. Have a mom and a dad.  Nakamura Sana is a bit skinny girl with dark brown hair and eyes. she\'s as tall as Suguru. Cries when Suguru acts mean towards her. Has one friend i.e., Suguru.  Everyone runs away because of her dad and also she\'s too shy to make friends, Suguru was the one who asked her to play together when she was playing alone in the park while all other children were playing together. They said she looked ugly skeleton and refused to play with her. Suguru even beat-up one or two kid who were badmouthing her. And later got scolded by his parents for getting involved in a fight. The kids he beat-up complained at his home. From that day on wards Sana and Suguru became very good friends.  ** little kids are bitches\' agree??.... JK...***  Suguru\'s mom and dad are really sweet and they are also nice towards Sana. They are highly disciplined people but not too stiff to the rules. Suguru is their only son. The three of them make a really sweet family.  Sana have a mom and Dad as well. Her dad is a tall man with a well built physique, and have dark brown hair that reaches his shoulders with an undercut. He usually tie them up. He\'s a sporty person. Has a partnership in a yacht business oversees (that\'s basically their source of income).  Sana\'s mom is a baker. Their home is designed with the bakery on the ground floor and the residence on the upper story. She has a bit delicate body. Her black hair goes down her shoulder and are often tied in a loose ponytail. She\'s not that tall between 5\'6\" to 5\'7\". She is a sweet person but scolds her husband at times. They make a sweet couple. He met her at her bakery first time.]]></string>
    <string name="chapter_1_oblivion_eren_s_eyes_opened_realizing_he_was_back_in_the_paths_laying_on_the_sand_where_zeke_once_was_there_were_no_chains_this_time_nothing_holding_him_back_as_he_saw_ymir_look_at_him_in_the_distance_her_eyes_were_no_longer_foggy_and_white_they_had_expression_and_determination_in_them_he_gulps_silently_hoping_that_whatever_ymir_has_in_mind_for_him_it_will_just_end_with_everyone_saved_she_isn_t_smiling_of_course_when_he_walks_towards_her_but_she_offers_her_hand_eren_takes_it_hesitantly_slowly_looking_down_at_ymir_wondering_what_would_happen_next_long_ago_after_he_kissed_historia_s_hand_he_had_accepted_his_fate_but_now_all_of_the_things_eren_had_done_made_him_question_what_he_was_leaving_behind_people_would_see_him_as_a_mass_murderer_someone_that_destroyed_the_world_because_he_couldn_t_forgive_what_it_did_to_him_what_it_took_quot_this_is_not_what_you_want_is_it_quot_no_it_never_was_all_eren_ever_wanted_was_to_see_the_ocean_with_armin_and_mikasa_to_witness_all_those_things_that_the_world_offered_in_the_books_armin_use_to_read_quot_you_wanted_freedom_didn_t_you_quot_he_swallows_because_he_knows_that_this_was_always_the_path_regardless_of_whether_eren_did_it_alone_or_not_the_silence_answers_ymir_s_question_as_she_turns_back_to_him_forcing_eren_to_follow_her_their_footsteps_echo_in_the_paths_following_each_other_quot_if_you_want_to_change_your_mistakes_change_the_past_there_is_a_cost_to_this_just_like_the_other_many_things_you_have_achieved_for_freedom_quot_eren_stops_looking_down_at_ymir_waiting_for_her_to_say_something_else_a_warning_a_demand_a_sacrifice_to_change_it_all_to_do_it_all_over_again_but_differently_quot_the_presence_of_your_past_and_present_selves_cannot_exist_in_the_timeline_when_the_time_comes_and_you_meet_your_past_self_you_must_devour_them_what_mistakes_you_made_in_the_past_can_be_erased_and_you_can_start_again_do_not_repeat_the_past_eren_only_you_can_change_it_quot_ymir_touches_his_cheek_gently_almost_like_a_mother_would_her_child_it_reminds_eren_of_those_nights_when_his_mother_knew_something_was_troubling_him_this_was_his_only_chance_the_only_chance_to_fix_everything_that_eren_did_he_never_wanted_to_hurt_his_friends_he_never_wanted_to_lose_sasha_or_hange_he_didn_t_want_to_die_either_and_here_he_was_being_offered_a_second_chance_by_the_founding_titan_quot_goodbye_eren_i_hope_this_is_the_last_time_we_meet_quot_when_he_wakes_up_he_can_t_quite_figure_out_where_he_is_only_that_trees_surround_him_big_ass_trees_as_captain_levi_put_it_once_eren_snorts_at_the_old_remark_looking_around_all_he_can_hear_is_the_wind_and_leaves_rustling_his_body_feels_still_and_mechanical_straps_tightening_against_his_body_in_an_uncomfortable_way_eren_looks_down_and_freezes_realizing_immediately_that_he_s_in_the_gear_that_was_created_after_the_marleyans_arrived_yelena_and_her_group_helped_advance_paradis_and_the_weaponry_hange_was_so_excited_they_could_barely_contain_themselves_he_had_never_really_used_the_gear_didn_t_take_to_it_very_well_at_first_eren_remembers_jean_always_teasing_him_about_the_gear_saying_it_was_like_the_old_days_in_the_training_corps_but_then_the_ground_starts_to_shake_violently_the_telltale_sound_of_titans_approaching_from_somewhere_right_titans_eren_stands_straight_flying_into_the_air_immediately_landing_on_a_high_branch_just_in_time_too_titans_surround_the_area_that_he_was_once_standing_in_teeth_gnawing_on_the_trunk_like_dogs_there_are_voices_down_below_and_flares_are_suddenly_shooting_into_the_air_above_eren_this_was_the_day_they_found_the_female_titan_annie_was_here_and_so_were_the_rest_of_his_friends_captain_levi_and_squad_levi_this_was_his_chance_and_eren_didn_t_have_time_to_think_all_the_steps_through_yet_he_flies_down_hiding_behind_trees_to_avoid_being_seen_by_the_survey_corps_following_them_through_the_trees_he_can_already_spot_squad_levi_running_through_the_path_with_their_horses_eren_takes_a_moment_to_witness_that_orou_petra_eld_and_gunther_are_still_alive_and_moving_despite_the_captain_telling_eren_that_his_squad_dying_was_never_his_fault_he_always_blamed_himself_the_female_titan_crashes_through_the_forest_running_at_top_speed_to_catch_the_squad_eren_launches_into_the_air_without_another_thought_attaching_himself_to_the_steaming_skin_of_the_female_as_she_runs_he_follows_her_his_hooks_attaching_to_her_flesh_near_her_nape_causing_the_titan_to_startle_halting_eren_spins_around_his_cape_helping_him_to_stay_hidden_as_annie_swerves_to_catch_his_wires_with_her_movements_eren_slices_her_fingers_off_first_circling_around_to_cut_her_shoulder_off_completely_he_does_the_same_with_her_other_arm_then_her_legs_causing_her_to_fall_flat_to_the_ground_there_are_gasps_and_wires_whirring_in_the_air_as_eren_lands_on_annie_s_titan_form_quot_annie_you_should_ve_gone_home_to_your_father_and_stayed_there_but_i_can_t_control_what_happens_now_only_i_can_fix_my_mistakes_and_i_m_sorry_quot_he_whispers_to_her_his_blades_cut_through_the_nape_before_annie_can_even_protect_herself_pulling_the_young_girl_right_out_eren_looks_down_at_her_marks_from_where_her_skin_was_connected_to_her_titan_form_start_to_steam_there_s_shouting_in_the_distance_but_all_eren_can_think_about_is_annie_deserves_to_go_home_just_like_the_rest_of_them_standing_up_with_her_in_his_arms_eren_looks_at_her_her_eyes_closed_and_no_emotion_showing_on_her_face_horses_hooves_pound_loudly_halting_below_the_steaming_titan_the_squad_stares_at_him_with_shock_quot_w_who_are_you_quot_quot_show_yourself_quot_quot_captain_what_should_we_do_quot_there_s_a_whole_shouting_match_happening_as_eren_stands_there_holding_annie_while_they_all_stare_at_captain_levi_the_man_stares_at_eren_with_a_bored_expression_but_there_are_questions_swirling_in_those_gunmetal_eyes_of_his_quot_show_yourself_soldier_quot_quot_my_apologies_captain_but_i_can_t_reveal_myself_what_i_can_do_is_offer_annie_leonhart_to_you_sir_quot_petra_comes_forward_with_her_blades_oluo_following_her_as_they_both_glare_at_eren_those_looks_of_disdain_and_anger_are_oblivious_to_eren_since_he_s_felt_them_on_him_for_years_sliding_down_the_steaming_flesh_eren_drops_annie_at_petra_s_feet_head_tilting_to_the_ground_to_hide_his_face_his_long_hair_curtains_around_him_hiding_his_beautiful_eyes_from_squad_levi_quot_come_with_us_please_quot_quot_eren_quot_levi_snaps_at_the_boy_already_knowing_he_d_expect_an_outburst_from_the_brat_the_minute_the_stranger_showed_up_the_stranger_stiffens_visibly_footsteps_halting_as_he_slowly_turns_toward_the_soldiers_only_giving_a_peek_of_what_was_underneath_while_eren_tries_to_get_the_stranger_to_come_with_them_levi_stares_at_the_gear_that_the_stranger_wears_it_s_completely_different_from_the_survey_corps_more_modern_in_a_way_too_he_can_t_help_but_wonder_if_the_stranger_got_it_done_especially_in_the_underground_or_did_it_all_themselves_quot_oi_brat_let_me_speak_to_him_for_a_minute_quot_quot_o_oh_right_sorry_sir_quot_levi_gets_off_his_horse_reaching_the_stranger_that_gracefully_interrupted_their_mission_to_get_to_erwin_he_already_knows_hange_will_have_a_field_day_with_this_new_discovery_they_ll_beg_for_levi_to_tell_them_all_the_details_over_dinner_quot_i_suggest_you_come_with_us_otherwise_this_could_turn_quite_shitty_in_a_few_seconds_quot_the_rest_of_the_scouts_causes_eren_to_flee_immediately_disappearing_from_the_captain_s_very_eyes_for_the_rest_of_his_time_in_the_forest_he_lingers_watching_every_move_that_the_survey_corps_makes_eren_follows_squad_levi_closely_and_the_rest_of_the_scouts_as_they_finally_leave_the_titan_forest_eventually_they_make_it_back_to_the_walls_orders_being_yelled_out_as_horses_are_lifted_over_the_walls_eren_can_see_annie_fiddling_with_the_cuffs_they_ve_put_her_probably_looking_for_her_ring_the_very_ring_that_was_now_in_eren_s_hand_as_he_stares_hoping_it_becomes_dark_soon_so_he_can_enter_though_it_might_be_harder_with_the_garrison_on_duty_at_all_times_during_the_night_even_so_as_the_sun_slowly_sets_he_makes_his_move_walking_through_the_dark_silently_there_is_no_titan_insight_and_it_leaves_him_to_get_to_the_walls_quicker_easily_getting_in_once_inside_he_stays_unmoving_for_a_moment_noticing_that_he_was_in_the_stohess_district_east_of_wall_sina_if_eren_could_remember_right_the_commander_made_a_plan_to_investigate_annie_as_she_was_a_suspect_after_the_expedition_there_are_people_everywhere_chatting_dancing_walking_home_eren_envies_them_and_their_ignorance_sometimes_he_wished_to_forget_everything_and_to_just_lay_still_feeling_the_wind_brush_against_his_tan_skin_after_walking_around_for_a_while_eren_finally_decides_to_call_it_a_night_finding_a_small_inn_at_an_affordable_price_the_room_is_small_but_has_a_decent_bed_and_desk_to_make_up_for_the_size_as_he_sits_down_he_embraces_the_darkness_as_he_lies_on_the_bed_eyes_slowly_fading_to_nothing_but_idle_dreams_it_s_months_and_months_before_eren_finally_devises_a_plan_to_get_to_trost_and_find_his_younger_self_he_knows_already_that_being_heard_and_seen_has_changed_the_course_of_this_timeline_it_s_not_like_it_could_do_much_though_if_eren_doesn_t_try_to_find_where_the_survey_corps_were_now_there_were_so_many_memories_to_go_through_and_yet_he_had_such_a_hard_time_remembering_it_all_now_ymir_said_that_there_would_be_consequences_was_remembering_the_past_one_of_them_eren_huffs_to_himself_going_further_into_the_district_to_find_proper_clothes_and_food_people_pass_him_chatting_aloud_children_running_around_chasing_each_other_he_sits_in_a_small_corner_watching_as_the_military_police_made_their_rounds_gambling_and_drinking_joining_the_survey_corps_could_be_his_best_option_to_get_to_where_he_wanted_to_get_eren_back_for_maria_s_sake_why_was_doing_this_have_to_be_so_complicated_all_he_ever_wanted_was_for_the_people_he_cared_about_to_be_safe_to_have_the_freedom_to_not_just_explore_the_sea_but_the_world_is_this_enough_to_get_back_what_eren_sacrificed_the_question_keeps_him_in_thought_for_the_rest_of_the_night_sitting_in_his_room_alone_as_dawn_approaches_there_s_shouting_outside_as_eren_snaps_out_of_his_thoughts_looking_out_the_window_there_were_people_down_there_and_by_the_looks_of_it_military_police_great_this_day_was_starting_off_so_positive_already_eren_grumbles_to_himself_as_he_freshes_up_momentarily_fixing_his_long_hair_in_the_mirror_the_shouting_increases_as_he_steps_onto_the_streets_head_tilted_down_to_avoid_any_potential_scouts_but_then_he_can_overhear_the_conversation_going_on_with_the_military_police_near_the_corner_quot_buncha_suicidal_maniacs_wastin_lives_like_to_go_outside_the_walls_now_they_want_us_to_find_some_damn_stranger_i_got_better_things_to_do_than_this_quot_eren_pauses_eyes_widening_quickly_as_he_scurries_away_to_hide_guess_the_captain_insisted_on_finding_him_or_something_or_maybe_the_commander_saw_potential_in_him_and_wanted_to_see_for_himself_who_the_savior_of_the_expedition_was_either_way_eren_knew_he_had_to_go_he_had_to_do_something_there_s_more_shouting_than_usual_as_eren_passes_almost_feeling_like_he_was_being_watched_in_the_distance_by_someone_keeping_pace_with_other_people_eren_blends_into_the_crowds_a_dark_hood_covering_his_face_from_anyone_s_view_he_shuffles_through_stopping_in_an_alleyway_to_avoid_any_more_suspicions_eren_can_t_do_anything_though_when_there_s_a_sensation_of_a_cold_breeze_above_wind_running_through_his_hood_he_detests_the_silence_that_follows_the_flags_of_the_king_swishing_in_the_air_eren_can_hear_children_laughing_in_the_distance_even_the_moment_pebbles_meet_cobblestone_a_flare_goes_off_distantly_and_it_s_green_shit_he_climbs_up_a_ladder_making_it_to_the_roof_in_time_to_see_scouts_flying_all_over_the_place_there_s_no_time_to_think_of_any_alternative_plan_leaving_eren_to_run_the_wind_blowing_his_cloak_through_the_air_grappling_hooks_almost_hit_him_along_the_way_scouts_flying_into_the_air_with_their_blades_there_is_no_time_to_play_games_with_them_and_eren_saw_this_as_a_chance_if_he_could_lead_them_all_in_different_directions_including_his_past_self_eren_could_snatch_the_kid_and_run_it_s_risky_but_it_was_worth_a_shot_instead_of_running_away_empty_every_time_a_scout_follows_eren_disappears_again_hiding_in_alleyways_or_anywhere_he_could_the_survey_corps_was_spread_out_including_squad_levi_all_spreading_out_to_find_this_mysterious_person_to_levi_he_found_it_pretty_astonishing_that_the_blonde_coconut_head_armin_was_able_to_guess_where_this_figure_could_be_heading_he_had_to_hand_it_to_erwin_to_always_find_the_good_ones_in_this_shitty_ass_world_it_also_seemed_like_the_stranger_was_certainly_experienced_with_the_odm_gear_letting_the_survey_corps_split_up_entirely_there_was_something_there_something_in_the_stranger_that_made_him_seem_familiar_to_levi_in_some_way_eren_turns_spotting_his_past_self_alone_good_this_was_his_chance_to_do_it_armin_would_be_proud_of_him_for_devising_this_plan_instead_of_taking_action_without_thinking_he_zips_past_his_two_friends_with_a_sorrowful_look_snatching_his_past_self_before_anyone_could_stop_him_the_titan_shifter_yanks_on_the_young_boy_s_jacket_continuing_into_the_air_with_the_fifteen_year_old_thrashing_against_him_quot_let_me_go_or_i_ll_go_titan_quot_the_boy_keeps_screaming_causing_attention_to_draw_towards_them_as_eren_swoops_low_to_avoid_being_seen_again_they_land_on_the_ground_for_a_moment_only_for_eren_to_knock_the_other_out_completely_sighing_in_relief_for_silence_it_s_time_for_me_to_go_now"><![CDATA[Chapter 1: Oblivion Eren\'s eyes opened, realizing he was back in the Paths, laying on the sand where Zeke once was. There were no chains this time, nothing holding him back as he saw Ymir look at him in the distance. Her eyes were no longer foggy and white, they had expression and determination in them. He gulps, silently hoping that whatever Ymir has in mind for him, it will just end with everyone saved. She isn\'t smiling of course when he walks towards her but she offers her hand. Eren takes it hesitantly, slowly looking down at Ymir, wondering what would happen next. Long ago, after he kissed Historia\'s hand, he had accepted his fate. But now, all of the things Eren had done made him question what he was leaving behind. People would see him as a mass murderer, someone that destroyed the world because he couldn\'t forgive what it did to him, what it took. \"This is not what you want, is it?\" No, it never was, all Eren ever wanted was to see the ocean with Armin and Mikasa. To witness all those things that the world offered in the books Armin use to read. \"You wanted freedom, didn\'t you?\" He swallows because he knows that this was always the path, regardless of whether Eren did it alone or not. The silence answers Ymir\'s question, as she turns back to him, forcing Eren to follow her. Their footsteps echo in the Paths, following each other. \"If you want to change your mistakes, change the past, there is a cost to this. Just like the other many things you have achieved for freedom.\" Eren stops, looking down at Ymir, waiting for her to say something else, a warning, a demand, a sacrifice to change it all. To do it all over again but differently. \"The presence of your past and present selves cannot exist in the timeline. When the time comes and you meet your past self, you must devour them. What mistakes you made in the past can be erased and you can start again. Do not repeat the past, Eren, only you can change it.\" Ymir touches his cheek gently, almost like a mother would her child. It reminds Eren of those nights when his mother knew something was troubling him. This was his only chance, the only chance to fix everything that Eren did. He never wanted to hurt his friends, he never wanted to lose Sasha or Hange. He didn\'t want to die either and here he was, being offered a second chance by the Founding Titan. \"Goodbye Eren, I hope this is the last time we meet.\" ____ When he wakes up, he can\'t quite figure out where he is, only that trees surround him. Big ass trees,as Captain Levi put it once, Eren snorts at the old remark. Looking around, all he can hear is the wind and leaves rustling. His body feels still and mechanical, straps tightening against his body in an uncomfortable way. Eren looks down and freezes, realizing immediately that he\'s in the gear that was created after the Marleyans arrived. Yelena and her group helped advance Paradis and the weaponry, Hange was so excited, they could barely contain themselves.He had never really used the gear, didn\'t take to it very well at first. Eren remembers Jean always teasing him about the gear, saying it was like the old days in the training corps. But then the ground starts to shake violently, the telltale sound of titans approaching from somewhere. Right, titans, Eren stands straight, flying into the air immediately, landing on a high branch just in time too. Titans surround the area that he was once standing in, teeth gnawing on the trunk like dogs. There are voices down below, and flares are suddenly shooting into the air above Eren. This was the day they found the Female Titan. Annie was here, and so were the rest of his friends, Captain Levi and Squad Levi. This was his chance, and Eren didn\'t have time to think all the steps through yet. He flies down, hiding behind trees to avoid being seen by the Survey Corps, following them through the trees. He can already spot Squad Levi, running through the path with their horses. Eren takes a moment to witness that Orou, Petra, Eld, and Gunther are still alive and moving. Despite the Captain telling Eren that his squad dying was never his fault, he always blamed himself. The Female Titan crashes through the forest, running at top speed to catch the squad. Eren launches into the air without another thought, attaching himself to the steaming skin of the Female as she runs. He follows her, his hooks attaching to her flesh near her nape, causing the titan to startle, halting. Eren spins around, his cape helping him to stay hidden as Annie swerves to catch his wires. With her movements, Eren slices her fingers off first, circling around to cut her shoulder off completely. He does the same with her other arm then her legs, causing her to fall flat to the ground. There are gasps and wires whirring in the air as Eren lands on Annie\'s titan form. \"Annie, you should\'ve gone home to your father and stayed there. But I can\'t control what happens now, only I can fix my mistakes, and I\'m sorry,\" he whispers to her. His blades cut through the nape before Annie can even protect herself, pulling the young girl right out. Eren looks down at her, marks from where her skin was connected to her titan form start to steam. There\'s shouting in the distance but all Eren can think about is… Annie deserves to go home just like the rest of them. Standing up with her in his arms, Eren looks at her, her eyes closed and no emotion showing on her face. Horses\' hooves pound loudly, halting below the steaming titan, the squad stares at him with shock. \"W-who are you?\" \"Show yourself!\" \"Captain, what should we do?\" There\'s a whole shouting match happening as Eren stands there, holding Annie while they all stare at Captain Levi. The man stares at Eren with a bored expression, but there are questions swirling in those gunmetal eyes of his. \"Show yourself, soldier.\" \"My apologies, Captain, but I can\'t reveal myself. What I can do is offer Annie Leonhart to you, sir.\" Petra comes forward with her blades, Oluo following her as they both glare at Eren. Those looks of disdain and anger are oblivious to Eren since he\'s felt them on him for years. Sliding down the steaming flesh, Eren drops Annie at Petra\'s feet, head tilting to the ground to hide his face. His long hair curtains around him, hiding his beautiful eyes from Squad Levi. \"Come with us! Please!\" \"Eren!\" Levi snaps at the boy, already knowing he\'d expect an outburst from the brat the minute the stranger showed up. The stranger stiffens visibly, footsteps halting as he slowly turns toward the soldiers, only giving a peek of what was underneath. While Eren tries to get the stranger to come with them, Levi stares at the gear that the stranger wears. It\'s completely different from the Survey Corps\', more modern in a way too. He can\'t help but wonder if the stranger got it done especially in the Underground or did it all themselves.\"Oi, brat, let me speak to him for a minute.\" \"O-oh, right, sorry sir.\" Levi gets off his horse, reaching the stranger that gracefully interrupted their mission to get to Erwin. He already knows Hange will have a field day with this new discovery. They\'ll beg for Levi to tell them all the details over dinner. \"I suggest you come with us, otherwise this could turn quite shitty in a few seconds.\" ____ The rest of the scouts causes Eren to flee immediately, disappearing from the captain\'s very eyes. For the rest of his time in the forest, he lingers, watching every move that the Survey Corps makes. Eren follows Squad Levi closely, and the rest of the scouts as they finally leave the titan forest. Eventually, they make it back to the walls, orders being yelled out as horses are lifted over the walls. Eren can see Annie fiddling with the cuffs they\'ve put her, probably looking for her ring. The very ring that was now in Eren\'s hand as he stares, hoping it becomes dark soon so he can enter. Though it might be harder with the Garrison on duty at all times during the night. Even so, as the sun slowly sets, he makes his move, walking through the dark silently. There is no titan insight and it leaves him to get to the walls quicker, easily getting in. Once inside, he stays unmoving for a moment, noticing that he was in the Stohess District, east of Wall Sina. If Eren could remember right, the Commander made a plan to investigate Annie as she was a suspect after the expedition. There are people everywhere, chatting, dancing, walking home; Eren envies them and their ignorance. Sometimes he wished to forget everything and to just lay still, feeling the wind brush against his tan skin. After walking around for a while, Eren finally decides to call it a night, finding a small inn at an affordable price. The room is small but has a decent bed and desk to make up for the size as he sits down. He embraces the darkness as he lies on the bed, eyes slowly fading to nothing but idle dreams. ____ It\'s months and months before Eren finally devises a plan to get to Trost and find his younger self. He knows already that being heard and seen has changed the course of this timeline. It\'s not like it could do much though if Eren doesn\'t try to find where the Survey Corps were now. There were so many memories to go through and yet he had such a hard time remembering it all now. Ymir said that there would be consequences, was remembering the past one of them? Eren huffs to himself, going further into the district to find proper clothes and food. People pass him, chatting aloud, children running around, chasing each other. He sits in a small corner, watching as the military police made their rounds, gambling, and drinking. Joining the Survey Corps could be his best option to get to where he wanted, to get Eren back. For Maria\'s sake, why was doing this have to be so complicated? All he ever wanted was for the people he cared about to be safe, to have the freedom to not just explore the sea, but the world. Is this enough to get back what Eren sacrificed? The question keeps him in thought for the rest of the night, sitting in his room alone as dawn approaches. There\'s shouting outside as Eren snaps out of his thoughts, looking out the window. There were people down there, and by the looks of it, Military Police. Great, this day was starting off so positive already. Eren grumbles to himself as he freshes up, momentarily fixing his long hair in the mirror. The shouting increases as he steps onto the streets, head tilted down to avoid any potential scouts. But then he can overhear the conversation going on with the military police near the corner. \"Buncha\' suicidal maniacs, wastin\' lives like to go outside the walls! Now they want us to find some damn stranger! I got better things to do than this!\"Eren pauses, eyes widening quickly as he scurries away to hide. Guess the Captain insisted on finding him or something. Or maybe the Commander saw potential in him and wanted to see for himself who the savior of the expedition was. Either way, Eren knew he had to go, he had to do something. There\'s more shouting than usual as Eren passes, almost feeling like he was being watched in the distance by someone. Keeping pace with other people, Eren blends into the crowds, a dark hood covering his face from anyone\'s view. He shuffles through, stopping in an alleyway to avoid any more suspicions. Eren can\'t do anything though when there\'s a sensation of a cold breeze above, wind running through his hood. He detests the silence that follows, the flags of the King swishing in the air. Eren can hear children laughing in the distance, even the moment pebbles meet cobblestone. A flare goes off distantly, and it\'s green, shit! He climbs up a ladder, making it to the roof in time to see scouts flying all over the place. There\'s no time to think of any alternative plan, leaving Eren to run, the wind blowing his cloak through the air. Grappling hooks almost hit him along the way, scouts flying into the air with their blades. There is no time to play games with them, and Eren saw this as a chance. If he could lead them all in different directions including his past self, Eren could snatch the kid and run. It\'s risky but it was worth a shot instead of running away empty. Every time a scout follows, Eren disappears again, hiding in alleyways or anywhere he could. The Survey Corps was spread out, including Squad Levi, all spreading out to find this mysterious person. To Levi, he found it pretty astonishing that the blonde coconut head, Armin, was able to guess where this figure could be heading. He had to hand it to Erwin to always find the good ones in this shitty-ass world. It also seemed like the stranger was certainly experienced with the ODM gear, letting the Survey Corps split up entirely. There was something there, something in the stranger that made him seem familiar to Levi in some way. Eren turns, spotting his past self alone, good, this was his chance to do it. Armin would be proud of him for devising this plan instead of taking action without thinking. He zips past his two friends with a sorrowful look, snatching his past self before anyone could stop him. The titan shifter yanks on the young boy\'s jacket, continuing into the air with the fifteen-year-old thrashing against him. \"Let me go! Or I\'ll go titan!\" The boy keeps screaming, causing attention to draw towards them as Eren swoops low to avoid being seen again. They land on the ground for a moment only for Eren to knock the other out completely, sighing in relief for silence. It\'s time for me to go now.]]></string>
    <string name="in_muscles_are_better_than_magic_a_boy_named_yuri_lives_in_the_forest_alone_he_has_managed_to_train_himself_to_the_point_where_he_s_super_ripped_and_can_take_on_anything_when_he_finds_an_elven_girl_named_filia_windia_he_decides_to_go_on_adventures_with_her_for_no_reason_whatsoever_if_muscles_appears_to_be_a_run_of_the_mill_typical_shounen_fantasy_light_novel_to_you_that_s_because_it_is_the_whole_darn_thing_is_the_two_of_them_hanging_out_a_lot_of_the_interactions_are_just_him_using_his_muscles_and_freaking_people_out_and_like_i_said_in_the_premise_there_s_no_purpose_to_anything_that_happens_they_just_go_on_adventures_that_are_no_different_from_your_typical_slice_of_life_fantasy_with_no_real_spice_beyond_yuri_s_muscles_the_mostly_boring_cast_doesn_t_help_either_while_yuri_and_filia_have_some_legitimately_cute_and_funny_interactions_they_are_surrounded_by_idiots_all_the_other_characters_are_inconsequential_npcs_who_have_no_personality_other_than_being_shocked_by_yuri_s_muscles_that_s_literally_it_but_even_then_yuri_is_also_incredibly_bland_with_filia_being_the_only_remotely_likeable_character_the_biggest_issue_is_the_writing_muscles_is_one_of_those_light_novels_that_feels_like_a_rough_draft_and_not_a_publication_although_the_action_scenes_are_pretty_good_descriptions_of_locations_are_as_bare_minimum_as_they_typically_are_in_these_series_i_get_that_writing_is_really_hard_but_that_doesn_t_excuse_when_it_s_bad_in_a_published_work_in_mashle_magic_and_muscles_a_boy_named_mash_burnedead_lives_in_the_forest_with_an_old_wizard_guy_he_was_born_in_a_world_of_magic_but_has_no_magic_himself_making_him_an_easy_target_of_the_police_when_he_bests_the_police_with_his_bare_hands_he_is_given_a_deal_enroll_in_magic_school_and_graduate_at_the_top_of_his_class_or_be_pursued_by_the_law_forever_he_accepts_the_deal_and_attends_the_school_with_no_magic_power_whatsoever_i_made_a_big_deal_about_how_muscles_and_mashle_are_the_same_but_it_turns_out_that_mashle_resembles_black_clover_more_than_anything_else_oops_in_any_case_mashle_already_shows_greater_personality_than_muscles_not_only_is_the_humor_and_its_delivery_much_more_substantial_than_in_muscles_but_there_s_also_a_purpose_to_the_shenanigans_that_ensue_so_far_mashle_s_biggest_issue_is_its_simplicity_while_i_love_a_good_clear_cut_jump_manga_a_lot_of_very_vocal_people_don_t_because_of_this_there_s_no_rhyme_or_reason_to_the_magic_that_gets_used_they_don_t_even_bother_to_explain_the_rules_and_of_course_let_s_not_forget_the_magic_word_unrealistic_because_of_how_impossibly_strong_mash_is_for_a_teenager_mashle_has_a_similar_issue_to_muscles_everyone_other_than_the_main_character_exists_just_to_react_to_how_swole_said_main_character_is_furthermore_the_lead_girl_is_less_remarkable_than_filia_to_the_point_where_i_already_forgot_her_name_but_unlike_yuri_mash_is_a_significantly_more_likeable_character_in_fact_he_s_the_bread_and_butter_of_this_whole_manga_while_he_s_completely_devoid_of_personality_the_author_somehow_makes_that_lack_of_personality_into_its_own_personality_quirk_also_his_inane_obsession_with_cream_puffs_makes_him_even_more_hilarious_the_art_doesn_t_look_like_much_but_it_s_more_than_enough_the_panel_composition_expertly_sells_the_humor_while_also_delivering_the_appropriate_amount_of_punch_to_mash_s_attacks_if_there_are_any_issues_it_s_that_the_black_wizard_robes_make_a_lot_of_the_foreshortening_shots_look_kind_of_weird">In Muscles Are Better Than Magic!, a boy named Yuri lives in the forest alone. He has managed to train himself to the point where he’s super ripped, and can take on anything. When he finds an elven girl named Filia Windia, he decides to go on adventures with her, for no reason whatsoever. If Muscles appears to be a run-of-the-mill, typical shounen fantasy light novel to you, that’s because it is! The whole darn thing is the two of them hanging out. A lot of the interactions are just him using his muscles and freaking people out. And like I said in the premise, there’s no purpose to anything that happens. They just go on adventures that are no different from your typical slice-of-life fantasy with no real spice beyond Yuri’s muscles. The mostly boring cast doesn’t help either. While Yuri and Filia have some legitimately cute and funny interactions, they are surrounded by idiots. All the other characters are inconsequential NPCs who have no personality other than being shocked by Yuri’s muscles. That’s literally it! But even then, Yuri is also incredibly bland, with Filia being the only remotely likeable character. The biggest issue is the writing. Muscles is one of those light novels that feels like a rough draft and not a publication. Although the action scenes are pretty good, descriptions of locations are as bare minimum as they typically are in these series. I get that writing is really hard but that doesn’t excuse when it’s bad in a published work!In Mashle: Magic and Muscles, a boy named Mash Burnedead lives in the forest with an old wizard guy. He was born in a world of magic, but has no magic himself, making him an easy target of the police. When he bests the police with his bare hands, he is given a deal: enroll in Magic School and graduate at the top of his class or be pursued by the law forever. He accepts the deal, and attends the school with no magic power whatsoever. I made a big deal about how Muscles and Mashle are the same, but… it turns out that Mashle resembles Black Clover more than anything else (oops). In any case, Mashle already shows greater personality than Muscles. Not only is the humor (and its delivery) much more substantial than in Muscles, but there’s also a purpose to the shenanigans that ensue. So far, Mashle’s biggest issue is its simplicity. While I love a good, clear-cut Jump manga, a lot of [very vocal] people don’t. Because of this, there’s no rhyme or reason to the magic that gets used; they don’t even bother to explain the rules. And of course, let’s not forget the magic word, “unrealistic”, because of how impossibly strong Mash is for a teenager. Mashle has a similar issue to Muscles: everyone other than the main character exists just to react to how swole said main character is. Furthermore, the lead girl is less remarkable than Filia, to the point where I already forgot her name. But unlike Yuri, Mash is a significantly more likeable character. In fact, he’s the bread and butter of this whole manga. While he’s completely devoid of personality, the author somehow makes that lack of personality into its own personality quirk. Also, his inane obsession with cream puffs makes him even more hilarious. The art doesn’t look like much, but it’s more than enough. The panel composition expertly sells the humor, while also delivering the appropriate amount of punch to Mash’s attacks. If there are any issues, it’s that the black wizard robes make a lot of the foreshortening shots look kind of weird.</string>
    <string name="deku_v_o_the_most_amazing_hero_in_the_entire_world_all_might_the_real_thing_in_the_flesh_standing_right_in_front_of_me_he_looks_so_much_cooler_in_person_holy_crap_i_gotta_get_an_autograph_i_ve_got_a_pen_around_here_somewhere_please_sign_my_notebook_screams_he_already_did_whimpering_thank_you_so_much_this_will_be_an_heirloom_a_family_treasure_passed_down_for_generations_to_come_uh_huh_well_i_ve_gotta_get_this_guy_to_the_police_so_they_can_take_care_of_him_stay_out_of_trouble_see_you_around_wait_you_re_leaving_already_pro_heroes_are_constantly_fighting_time_as_well_as_enemies_deku_v_o_he_can_t_go_yet_there_s_still_so_many_questions_i_have_to_ask_him_now_stand_back_i_m_taking_off_yells_thanks_for_your_continued_support_huh_screaming_hey_hey_hey_what_do_you_think_you_re_doing_let_go_i_love_my_fans_but_this_is_too_much_no_way_we_re_flying_if_i_let_go_now_i_ll_die_oh_that_s_a_good_point_i_just_have_a_lot_of_things_i_want_to_ask_you_personally_you_re_my_all_time_favourite_hero_all_might_please_okay_okay_i_get_it_just_keep_your_eyes_and_mouth_shut_sighs_coughing_shit_explosive_rumble_whimpering_my_whole_life_just_flashed_before_my_eyes_not_a_very_smart_move_bang_on_the_door_for_a_while_someone_will_let_you_in_now_i_have_to_go_see_you_on_the_flip_side_wait_not_yet_one_second_no_i_don_t_have_any_time_i_have_to_know_doctor_v_o_sorry_kid_it_s_not_gonna_happen_deku_s_mom_v_o_i_m_sorry_izuku_i_wish_things_were_different_bakugo_v_o_defenseless_izuku_the_school_s_already_crappy_you_really_wanna_embarrass_it_more_by_failing_so_hard_deku_sometimes_i_do_feel_like_i_m_a_failure_like_there_s_no_hope_for_me_but_even_so_i_m_not_gonna_give_up_ever_is_it_possible_to_become_a_hero_even_if_i_don_t_have_a_quirk_i_m_a_normal_kid_without_any_powers_could_i_ever_hope_to_be_someone_like_you_music_swells_deku_v_o_meeting_all_might_was_a_dream_come_true_a_real_miracle_standing_in_front_of_me_was_the_hero_i_idolised_most_of_my_life_i_didn_t_realise_it_at_the_time_but_that_chance_encounter_would_change_the_course_of_my_future_preview_all_might_v_o_never_fear_adoring_public_preview_all_might_v_o_never_fear_adoring_public_i_am_here_for_the_next_episode_preview_that_goo_villain_has_taken_a_boy_hostage_and_is_running_amok_in_the_town_this_isn_t_good_but_i_can_t_use_my_powers_much_longer_or_groans_you_re_pathetic_fraud_all_might">DEKU [V/O]: The most amazing hero in the entire world... All Might... the real thing... in the flesh... standing right in front of me! He looks so much cooler in person! Holy crap, I gotta get an autograph. I\'ve got a pen around here somewhere... Please sign my notebook. [screams] He already did! [whimpering] Thank you so much! This will be an heirloom, a family treasure passed down for generations to come! Uh-huh! Well, I\'ve gotta get this guy to the police so they can take care of him. Stay out of trouble, see you around! Wait... you\'re leaving? - Already? - Pro heroes are constantly fighting time as well as enemies! DEKU [V/O]: He can\'t go yet. There\'s still so many questions I have to ask him... Now stand back, I\'m taking off! [yells] Thanks for your continued support! Huh? [screaming] Hey, hey, hey! What do you think you\'re doing?! Let go! I love my fans but this is too much! No way, we\'re flying! If I let go now, I\'ll die! Oh, that\'s a good point. I just have a lot... of things I want to ask you, personally. You\'re my all-time favourite hero, All Might please! Okay, okay! I get it. Just keep your eyes and mouth shut. # # [sighs] [coughing] Shit! [explosive rumble] [whimpering] My whole life just flashed before my eyes. Not a very smart move. Bang on the door for a while, someone will let you in. Now, I have to go. See you on the flip side. Wait, not yet. - One second! - No! I don\'t have any time. I have to know! DOCTOR [V/O]: Sorry kid, it\'s not gonna happen... DEKU\'S MOM [V/O]: I\'m sorry, Izuku... I wish things were different... BAKUGO [V/O]: Defenseless Izuku! The school\'s already crappy, you really wanna embarrass it more by failing so hard? DEKU: Sometimes I do feel like I\'m a failure... like there\'s no hope for me. But even so... I\'m not gonna give up, ever! # # Is it possible to become a hero, even if I don\'t have a Quirk? I\'m a normal kid without any powers. Could I ever hope to be someone like you? # Music swells # DEKU [V/O]: Meeting All Might was a dream come true. A real miracle. Standing in front of me was the hero I idolised most of my life. I didn\'t realise it at the time, but that chance encounter would change the course of my future. # # PREVIEW ALL MIGHT [V/O]: Never fear, adoring public! PREVIEW ALL MIGHT [V/O]: Never fear, adoring public! I am here! For the next episode preview! That goo villain has taken a boy hostage and is running amok in the town? This isn\'t good! But... I can\'t use my powers much longer or... [groans] You\'re pathetic, fraud All Might!</string>
    <string name="chapter_1_kakigori_1_saitama_watched_tv_in_his_new_room_in_the_hero_association_hq_he_found_comedies_and_thrillers_particularly_interesting_but_the_fact_that_genos_had_to_interrupt_him_every_time_a_new_episode_came_on_seemed_to_get_on_his_nerves_quot_hey_sensei_do_you_believe_in_shooting_stars_quot_genos_asked_sitting_upright_saitama_needed_clarification_on_whether_genos_was_asking_him_this_question_as_a_joke_or_if_he_was_for_real_saitama_cleared_his_throat_quot_umm_no_i_don_t_why_did_you_ask_me_that_question_quot_quot_i_just_saw_that_there_will_be_a_stargazing_event_happening_on_the_west_side_of_city_a_we_could_chill_there_of_course_i_m_not_forcing_anything_on_you_i_m_just_saying_that_it_is_possible_to_catch_some_stars_master_saitama_quot_quot_eh_i_ll_pass_maybe_is_there_a_monster_on_the_way_there_there_seem_to_be_more_monsters_appearing_than_ever_before_quot_quot_according_to_my_knowledge_more_than_likely_are_you_mainly_interested_in_just_fighting_quot_quot_i_would_like_to_see_you_fight_you_just_got_an_upgrade_and_i_have_yet_to_see_you_in_action_against_a_monster_although_i_did_hear_that_you_went_against_a_dragon_level_threat_or_whatever_it_is_that_they_call_it_quot_quot_i_did_and_that_abomination_didn_t_give_me_too_much_of_a_problem_either_well_i_can_show_you_more_of_my_strength_on_our_way_to_the_location_i_m_getting_the_blankets_quot_genos_got_up_and_walked_to_the_closet_he_grabbed_the_blankets_and_stuffed_them_in_a_bag_when_he_got_back_saitama_was_putting_on_his_flip_flops_why_doesn_t_master_get_new_attire_after_all_he_s_got_more_yen_now_so_there_shouldn_t_be_any_excuse_maybe_he_s_still_a_simple_person_genos_thought_quot_ah_almost_forgot_let_s_get_some_kakigori_on_our_way_there_too_i_m_in_the_mood_for_it_quot_quot_no_problem_quot_genos_replied_saitama_and_genos_were_about_to_leave_the_room_but_saitama_walked_back_and_turned_off_the_tv_he_would_always_remember_to_do_it_in_his_old_apartment_but_he_could_see_himself_quickly_forgetting_in_a_space_this_luxurious_2_saitama_and_genos_walked_in_the_streets_of_city_a_eating_kakigori_saitama_grinned_with_pleasure_obviously_taking_more_joy_in_eating_it_than_genos_as_they_made_a_right_turn_on_another_street_barely_crossing_over_before_a_car_attempted_to_run_them_over_a_paper_flew_into_genos_s_hand_it_was_a_newspaper_genos_looked_it_over_and_raised_his_eyebrows_heroes_from_the_hero_association_join_the_neo_heroes_which_association_is_better_for_our_world_saitama_mindlessly_thinks_about_eating_another_kakigori_until_genos_taps_him_on_the_shoulder_quot_master_it_seems_the_hero_association_is_starting_to_lose_recognition_the_neo_heroes_are_trying_to_take_their_place_what_do_you_think_quot_quot_don_t_know_don_t_care_quot_quot_but_master_this_may_be_serious_what_if_quot_genos_s_kakigori_flies_out_of_his_hand_so_fast_that_he_almost_thinks_master_saitama_has_pushed_him_it_turns_out_that_there_was_a_monster_in_front_of_them_both_genos_and_saitama_leaped_back_and_stood_their_ground_demon_level_threat_kakigori_quot_i_don_t_get_it_why_doesn_t_anyone_love_kakigori_as_i_do_you_people_are_insane_you_incompetent_animals_don_t_deserve_to_live_anymore_quot_kakigori_screamed_just_like_genos_had_already_figured_out_the_monster_was_made_out_of_pure_slushy_which_meant_its_durability_wasn_t_that_high_indeed_he_could_make_quick_work_out_of_this_weakling_genos_got_in_his_battle_stance_quot_watch_master_as_i_exterminate_the_monster_this_is_a_testament_to_doctor_kuseno_s_work_quot_quot_sure_go_ahead_quot_saitama_replied_genos_dashed_at_the_monster_at_full_speed_kakigori_didn_t_even_notice_he_had_moved_by_the_time_he_did_it_was_already_too_late_kakigori_s_upper_body_was_destroyed_immediately_after_genos_s_punch_connected_the_impact_of_genos_s_punch_sent_six_cars_flying_in_all_directions_saitama_knew_that_genos_didn_t_even_try_to_punch_that_monster_genos_has_gotten_stronger_saitama_thought_as_genos_walked_away_from_kakigori_s_corpse_he_sensed_another_danger_quot_saitama_sensei_behind_you_quot_genos_screamed_saitama_lifted_his_right_hand_and_barely_punched_the_slushy_monster_about_to_attack_him_completely_disintegrating_it_genos_spotted_four_other_slushy_monsters_on_top_of_the_buildings_when_he_reached_saitama_they_were_multiplying_at_a_fast_rate_above_them_quot_master_they_can_multiply_we_must_kill_as_many_of_them_as_possible_before_it_s_too_late_quot_genos_said_quot_alright_geez_well_they_re_going_in_our_direction_anyway_so_it_s_not_too_bad_quot_saitama_replied_genos_used_his_boosters_to_launch_himself_from_building_to_building_eventually_he_was_going_at_about_200_mph_he_was_still_amazed_that_saitama_sensei_was_catching_up_to_him_with_no_problem_he_was_even_more_amazed_when_he_realized_that_he_lost_track_of_all_the_kakigori_clones_even_at_this_speed_unbelievable_i_let_my_guard_down_again_and_now_i_can_t_find_them_all_the_civilians_have_scattered_and_this_monster_hasn_t_been_public_for_over_twenty_minutes_that_s_a_good_thing_but_genos_stops_at_one_building_and_sees_a_car_driving_northeast_to_genos_he_knows_that_this_isn_t_any_ordinary_car_it_had_to_have_belonged_to_the_blizzard_group_saitama_strolled_next_to_genos_quot_master_i_think_fubuki_and_her_group_are_going_after_that_monster_quot_quot_no_way_didn_t_she_quit_that_group_a_while_back_quot_quot_she_did_quot_quot_yeah_i_found_out_from_that_green_haired_child_after_she_was_trying_to_mess_with_me_quot_quot_quot_quot_what_s_wrong_quot_quot_nothing_say_if_that_wasn_t_the_blizzard_group_then_quot_quot_whatever_it_is_we_can_worry_about_it_later_maybe_some_other_a_class_heroes_will_take_care_of_that_thing_quot_saitama_replied_quot_i_doubt_it_master_the_monster_can_multiply_maybe_it_has_similar_abilities_to_black_sperm_if_that_s_the_case_we_can_t_let_it_combine_who_knows_if_it_will_become_a_dragon_level_threat_quot_quot_man_i_wasn_t_expecting_this_to_go_on_whatever_we_re_just_going_to_miss_the_stars_quot_saitama_replied_saitama_and_genos_followed_the_car_3_the_car_makes_a_left_turn_its_main_goal_was_to_follow_the_slushy_monsters_but_now_that_they_had_seemingly_lost_all_of_the_clones_they_devised_a_new_plan_quot_i_see_two_other_heroes_following_us_i_bet_they_re_a_class_maybe_we_can_work_with_them_and_split_the_pay_when_we_capture_the_monster_quot_ting_said_as_he_tried_to_park_saitama_and_genos_stopped_at_a_building_saitama_scratched_his_bald_head_quot_looks_like_they_ve_spotted_us_master_quot_quot_oh_that_explains_everything_quot_saitama_and_genos_jumped_off_the_building_and_landed_next_to_the_lamborghini_only_two_people_got_out_of_the_vehicle_both_of_them_were_presumably_working_for_the_neo_heroes_they_wore_battle_suits_quot_why_are_you_guys_driving_a_car_when_you_re_strong_enough_to_travel_in_those_suits_quot_genos_asked_quot_we_re_trying_to_trick_the_monster_into_underestimating_us_it_works_with_many_monsters_we_find_and_beat_up_oh_by_the_way_my_name_is_ting_i_m_one_of_the_neo_heroes_and_this_is_hoppi_we_re_sort_of_a_duo_why_are_you_following_us_quot_hoppi_said_quot_we_originally_thought_that_you_guys_were_a_part_of_the_blizzard_group_but_then_noticed_the_sign_on_your_vehicle_you_really_are_a_part_of_the_neo_heroes_are_you_willing_to_help_us_catch_the_monster_quot_genos_replied_maybe_i_can_trick_them_into_thinking_genos_began_quot_sure_but_only_if_you_re_willing_to_split_the_payment_quot_saitama_frowned_genos_sighed_quot_whatever_genos_as_long_as_the_monster_s_put_down_that_s_all_that_matters_right_quot_saitama_said_genos_froze_up_he_stared_at_the_grown_and_gradually_looked_up_quot_you_re_right_as_long_as_the_monster_is_put_down_quot_genos_dashed_away_from_saitama_so_fast_that_the_pavement_crumbled_saitama_raised_his_eyebrows_quot_welp_snooze_you_lose_quot_saitama_said_and_did_the_same_both_heroes_ran_so_fast_that_ting_and_hoppi_couldn_t_keep_up_with_which_direction_they_were_going_quot_shit_they_re_leaving_us_don_t_leave_the_car_follow_me_quot_ting_said_he_sprinted_in_their_direction_if_anything_he_needed_to_kill_that_monster_before_those_two_heroes_did_hoppi_hopped_in_the_car_and_followed_ting_4_kakigori_landed_on_a_dumpster_when_he_tripped_and_fell_off_a_building_he_cried_in_surprise_had_he_been_going_too_fast_for_comfort_to_escape_those_heroes_no_definitely_not_i_did_them_a_good_deed_after_all_i_don_t_have_to_worry_about_killing_them_now_that_i_have_escaped_but_if_i_call_all_my_clones_to_combine_they_might_have_a_chance_of_finding_me_oh_whatever_they_don_t_look_like_they_can_contest_against_a_dragon_level_threat_anyway_kakigori_got_up_and_made_clicking_sounds_the_sounds_that_he_made_produced_sound_waves_that_only_his_clones_could_hear_humans_can_t_hear_these_waves_by_the_time_he_stopped_clicking_two_of_his_clones_had_already_arrived_in_his_location_i_m_hoping_there_will_be_more_than_fifty_of_them_by_now_kakigori_waited_some_more_and_eventually_all_the_clones_came_to_him_in_total_there_were_about_45_clones_kakigori_snapped_his_fingers_together_and_all_the_clones_started_coming_to_each_other_one_by_one_they_all_combined_into_one_powerful_being_that_was_just_above_a_dragon_level_threat_dragon_level_threat_supreme_kakigori_supreme_kakigori_made_a_battle_stance_next_to_the_dumpster_he_had_just_fallen_on_a_while_ago_he_grinned_now_it_s_time_for_those_heroes_to_meet_their_demise_supreme_kakigori_jumped_over_the_face_and_stood_in_the_middle_of_the_road_he_glanced_to_the_right_and_saw_a_car_coming_in_his_direction_it_was_unexpectedly_going_pretty_fast_for_a_car_at_least_he_waited_for_the_car_to_reach_him_when_it_did_it_stopped_only_four_feet_away_with_its_headlights_beaming_in_his_eyes_i_ll_swiftly_consume_the_fluids_of_this_human_once_it_supreme_kakigori_s_head_screamed_at_him_to_leap_sideways_so_he_did_he_had_managed_to_dodge_the_smash_of_another_hero_that_came_out_of_nowhere_he_landed_on_a_nearby_vehicle_completely_caving_the_top_of_the_vehicle_inside_the_car_with_his_two_feet_his_eyes_lit_up_ah_i_see_they_aren_t_from_the_hero_association_these_are_neo_heroes_what_a_joke_kakigori_thought_he_got_back_in_his_battle_stance_the_neo_hero_who_tried_to_kill_him_had_almost_destroyed_the_entire_city_block_still_this_was_nothing_to_supreme_kakigori_quot_what_i_didn_t_know_you_could_move_so_fast_quot_the_neo_hero_screamed_leaning_up_quot_i_know_right_quot_kakigori_said_standing_behind_the_neo_hero_quot_what_the_quot_the_hero_said_right_before_kakigori_punched_him_through_multiple_buildings_already_on_the_verge_of_falling_apart_quot_hoppi_quot_the_other_neo_hero_who_got_out_of_the_lamborghini_said_kakigori_turned_in_his_direction_and_grinned_before_he_could_take_another_step_forward_he_felt_the_bottom_of_someone_s_feet_graze_his_face_the_ground_around_him_shattered_it_had_been_hoppi_who_quickly_recovered_from_his_punch_and_paid_it_back_with_a_full_blown_kick_however_it_was_clearly_ineffective_as_supreme_kakigori_didn_t_move_an_inch_quot_you_re_durable_enough_but_that_s_only_the_suit_your_strength_is_weak_quot_supreme_kakigori_said_hoppi_gave_a_nervous_smile_quot_yeah_well_how_about_this_quot_hoppi_screamed_he_used_the_leg_that_he_kicked_supreme_kakigori_with_to_boost_himself_in_the_air_and_pulled_out_his_energy_swords_blood_washed_down_his_face_from_his_forehead_quot_it_looks_like_you_barely_managed_to_survive_that_punch_if_you_back_off_and_run_i_might_spare_you_or_i_could_just_kill_you_where_you_stand_quot_supreme_kakigori_said_supreme_kakigori_ripped_off_his_arm_and_waited_for_it_to_regenerate_when_it_did_it_turned_into_a_more_muscular_and_dense_one_he_could_tell_the_neo_heroes_were_now_more_afraid_than_ever_the_other_neo_hero_twenty_feet_behind_him_standing_next_to_the_totaled_car_got_out_his_energy_swords_too_ah_i_see_what_they_re_doing_they_re_trying_to_charge_up_their_suits_for_a_barrage_attack_they_can_charge_up_all_they_want_because_i_m_about_to_put_this_joint_in_the_ground_when_hoppi_and_the_other_neo_hero_charged_at_him_at_unimaginable_speeds_supreme_kakigori_smashed_the_ground_with_the_fist_from_his_muscular_arm_an_enormous_shockwave_occurred_destroying_multiple_city_blocks_in_all_directions"><![CDATA[Chapter 1 Kakigori 1 Saitama watched TV in his new room in the Hero Association HQ. He found comedies and thrillers particularly interesting, but the fact that Genos had to interrupt him every time a new episode came on seemed to get on his nerves. \"Hey, Sensei, do you believe in shooting stars?\" Genos asked, sitting upright. Saitama needed clarification on whether Genos was asking him this question as a joke or if he was for real. Saitama cleared his throat. \"Umm...no, I don\'t. Why did you ask me that question?\" \"I just saw that there will be a stargazing event happening on the west side of City A. We could chill there. Of course, I\'m not forcing anything on you. I\'m just saying that it is possible to catch some stars, Master Saitama.\" \"Eh...I\'ll pass, maybe. Is there a monster on the way there? There seem to be more monsters appearing than ever before.\" \"According to my knowledge, more than likely. Are you mainly interested in just fighting?\" \"I would like to see you fight. You just got an upgrade, and I have yet to see you in action against a monster. Although, I did hear that you went against a Dragon Level Threat, or whatever it is that they call it.\" \"I did, and that abomination didn\'t give me too much of a problem either. Well, I can show you more of my strength on our way to the location. I\'m getting the blankets.\" Genos got up and walked to the closet. He grabbed the blankets and stuffed them in a bag. When he got back, Saitama was putting on his flip-flops. Why doesn\'t Master get new attire? After all, he\'s got more yen now, so there shouldn\'t be any excuse. Maybe he\'s still a simple person, Genos thought. \"Ah...almost forgot, let\'s get some kakigori on our way there too. I\'m in the mood for it.\" \"No problem.\" Genos replied. Saitama and Genos were about to leave the room, but Saitama walked back and turned off the TV. He would always remember to do it in his old apartment, but he could see himself quickly forgetting in a space this luxurious. 2 Saitama and Genos walked in the streets of City A, eating kakigori. Saitama grinned with pleasure, obviously taking more joy in eating it than Genos. As they made a right turn on another street, barely crossing over before a car attempted to run them over, a paper flew into Genos\'s hand. It was a newspaper. Genos looked it over and raised his eyebrows: HEROES FROM THE HERO ASSOCIATION JOIN THE NEO HEROES! WHICH ASSOCIATION IS BETTER FOR OUR WORLD?! Saitama mindlessly thinks about eating another kakigori until Genos taps him on the shoulder. \"Master, it seems the Hero Association is starting to lose recognition. The Neo Heroes are trying to take their place. What do you think?\" \"Don\'t know, don\'t care.\" \"But Master, this may be serious...what if...\" Genos\'s kakigori flies out of his hand so fast that he almost thinks Master Saitama has pushed him. It turns out that there was a monster in front of them both. Genos and Saitama leaped back and stood their ground. DEMON LEVEL THREAT: KAKIGORI \"I DON\'T GET IT! WHY DOESN\'T ANYONE LOVE KAKIGORI AS I DO?! YOU, PEOPLE, ARE INSANE! YOU INCOMPETENT ANIMALS DON\'T DESERVE TO LIVE ANYMORE!\" Kakigori screamed. Just like Genos had already figured out, the monster was made out of pure slushy, which meant its durability wasn\'t that high. Indeed, he could make quick work out of this weakling. Genos got in his battle stance.\"Watch, Master, as I exterminate the monster. This is a testament to Doctor Kuseno\'s work.\" \"Sure...go ahead,\" Saitama replied. Genos dashed at the monster at full speed. Kakigori didn\'t even notice he had moved; by the time he did, it was already too late. Kakigori\'s upper body was destroyed immediately after Genos\'s punch connected. The impact of Genos\'s punch sent six cars flying in all directions. Saitama knew that Genos didn\'t even try to punch that monster. Genos has gotten stronger. Saitama thought. As Genos walked away from Kakigori\'s corpse, he sensed another danger. \"Saitama Sensei! Behind you!\" Genos screamed. Saitama lifted his right hand and barely punched the slushy monster about to attack him, completely disintegrating it. Genos spotted four other slushy monsters on top of the buildings when he reached Saitama. They were multiplying at a fast rate above them. \"Master, they can multiply! We must kill as many of them as possible before it\'s too late!\" Genos said. \"Alright, geez. Well, they\'re going in our direction anyway, so it\'s not too bad.\" Saitama replied. Genos used his boosters to launch himself from building to building. Eventually, he was going at about 200 MPH. He was still amazed that Saitama Sensei was catching up to him with no problem. He was even more amazed when he realized that he lost track of all the Kakigori clones even at this speed. Unbelievable, I let my guard down again, and now I can\'t find them. All the civilians have scattered, and this monster hasn\'t been public for over twenty minutes! That\'s a good thing, but... Genos stops at one building and sees a car driving northeast. To Genos, he knows that this isn\'t any ordinary car—it had to have belonged to the Blizzard Group. Saitama strolled next to Genos. \"Master, I think Fubuki and her group are going after that monster.\" \"No way. Didn\'t she quit that group a while back?\" \"She did?\" \"Yeah, I found out from that green-haired child after she was trying to mess with me.\" \". . .\" \"What\'s wrong?\" \"Nothing. Say, if that wasn\'t the Blizzard Group, then...\" \"Whatever it is, we can worry about it later. Maybe some other A-Class heroes will take care of that thing.\" Saitama replied. \"I doubt it, Master. The monster can multiply. Maybe it has similar abilities to Black Sperm. If that\'s the case, we can\'t let it combine. Who knows if it will become a Dragon Level Threat.\" \"Man...I wasn\'t expecting this to go on. Whatever, we\'re just going to miss the stars.\" Saitama replied. Saitama and Genos followed the car. 3 The car makes a left turn. Its main goal was to follow the slushy monsters, but now that they had seemingly lost all of the clones, they devised a new plan. \"I see two other heroes following us. I bet they\'re A-Class. Maybe we can work with them and split the pay when we capture the monster.\" Ting said as he tried to park. Saitama and Genos stopped at a building. Saitama scratched his bald head. \"Looks like they\'ve spotted us, Master.\" \"Oh, that explains everything.\" Saitama and Genos jumped off the building and landed next to the Lamborghini. Only two people got out of the vehicle. Both of them were presumably working for the Neo Heroes. They wore battle suits. \"Why are you guys driving a car when you\'re strong enough to travel in those suits?\" Genos asked. \"We\'re trying to trick the monster into underestimating us. It works with many monsters we find and beat up. Oh, by the way, my name is Ting, I\'m one of the Neo Heroes, and this is Hoppi. We\'re sort of a duo. Why are you following us?\" Hoppi said. \"We originally thought that you guys were a part of the Blizzard Group, but then noticed the sign on your vehicle. You really are a part of the Neo Heroes. Are you willing to help us catch the monster?\" Genos replied. Maybe I can trick them into thinking...Genos began.\"Sure, but only if you\'re willing to split the payment.\" Saitama frowned. Genos sighed. \"Whatever, Genos, as long as the monster\'s put down. That\'s all that matters...right?\" Saitama said. Genos froze up. He stared at the grown and gradually looked up. \"You\'re right, as long as the monster is put down...\" Genos dashed away from Saitama so fast that the pavement crumbled. Saitama raised his eyebrows. \"Welp, snooze, you lose,\" Saitama said and did the same. Both heroes ran so fast that Ting and Hoppi couldn\'t keep up with which direction they were going. \"Shit, they\'re leaving us. Don\'t leave the car! Follow me!\" Ting said. He sprinted in their direction. If anything, he needed to kill that monster before those two heroes did. Hoppi hopped in the car and followed Ting. 4 Kakigori landed on a dumpster when he tripped and fell off a building. He cried in surprise. Had he been going too fast for comfort to escape those heroes? No, definitely not. I did them a good deed. After all, I don\'t have to worry about killing them now that I have escaped. But...if I call all my clones to combine, they might have a chance of finding me. Oh, whatever. They don\'t look like they can contest against a Dragon Level Threat anyway. Kakigori got up and made clicking sounds. The sounds that he made produced sound waves that only his clones could hear. Humans can\'t hear these waves. By the time he stopped clicking, two of his clones had already arrived in his location. I\'m hoping there will be more than fifty of them by now. Kakigori waited some more, and eventually, all the clones came to him. In total, there were about 45 clones. Kakigori snapped his fingers together, and all the clones started coming to each other. One by one, they all combined into one powerful being that was just above a Dragon Level Threat. DRAGON LEVEL THREAT: SUPREME KAKIGORI. Supreme Kakigori made a battle stance next to the dumpster he had just fallen on a while ago. He grinned. Now, it\'s time for those heroes to meet their demise. Supreme Kakigori jumped over the face and stood in the middle of the road. He glanced to the right and saw a car coming in his direction. It was unexpectedly going pretty fast—for a car, at least. He waited for the car to reach him. When it did, it stopped only four feet away, with its headlights beaming in his eyes. I\'ll swiftly consume the fluids of this human once it... Supreme Kakigori\'s head screamed at him to leap sideways, so he did. He had managed to dodge the smash of another hero that came out of nowhere. He landed on a nearby vehicle, completely caving the top of the vehicle inside the car with his two feet. His eyes lit up. Ah, I see. They aren\'t from the Hero Association. These are Neo Heroes. What a joke...Kakigori thought. He got back in his battle stance. The Neo Hero who tried to kill him had almost destroyed the entire city block. Still, this was nothing to Supreme Kakigori. \"WHAT?! I didn\'t know you could move so fast!\" The Neo Hero screamed, leaning up. \"I know, right?\" Kakigori said, standing behind the Neo Hero. \"What the...\" The hero said right before Kakigori punched him through multiple buildings already on the verge of falling apart. \"HOPPI!\" The other Neo Hero who got out of the Lamborghini said. Kakigori turned in his direction and grinned. Before he could take another step forward, he felt the bottom of someone\'s feet graze his face. The ground around him shattered. It had been Hoppi who quickly recovered from his punch and paid it back with a full-blown kick. However, it was clearly ineffective, as Supreme Kakigori didn\'t move an inch. \"You\'re durable enough, but that\'s only the suit. Your strength is weak.\" Supreme Kakigori said. Hoppi gave a nervous smile. \"Yeah, well, how about this?!\" Hoppi screamed. He used the leg that he kicked Supreme Kakigori with to boost himself in the air and pulled out his energy swords. Blood washed down his face from his forehead.\"It looks like you barely managed to survive that punch. If you back off and run, I might spare you. Or, I could just kill you where you stand.\" Supreme Kakigori said. Supreme Kakigori ripped off his arm and waited for it to regenerate. When it did, it turned into a more muscular and dense one. He could tell the Neo Heroes were now more afraid than ever. The other Neo Hero, twenty feet behind him, standing next to the totaled car, got out his energy swords too. Ah, I see what they\'re doing. They\'re trying to charge up their suits for a barrage attack. They can charge up all they want because I\'m about to put this joint in the ground. When Hoppi and the other Neo Hero charged at him at unimaginable speeds, Supreme Kakigori smashed the ground with the fist from his muscular arm. An enormous shockwave occurred, destroying multiple city blocks in all directions...]]></string>
</resources>